Guide to the Time Inc. Annual Reports 1922-2016 MS 3009-RG 31
New-York Historical Society
Time Inc. Annual Reports
1922-2016
New-York Historical Society
Time, inc.
MS 3009-RG 31
8 Linear feet in 8 record cartons
Time Inc. Annual Reports includes annual reports for Time Inc. and later Time Warner Inc. after the merger in 1989; and annual reports from America Online, Inc. (AOL) sent to the library for use as reference at the time of that merger.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Time Inc. in 2015.
Related Archival Materials Note
This finding aid relates to just one record group of the Time Inc. Records. For information about the other record groups and for overall information about the archives, please see the Guide to the Time Inc. Records (MS 3009). The Henry Luce Papers (MS 3014) were acquired with the Time Inc. Records. The collection of books acquired with the records are cataloged as the Time Inc. Reference Library.
Access Restrictions
OMaterials in this collection are stored offsite. For more information on making arrangements to consult them, please visit www.nyhistory.org/library/visit.
Arrangement Note
Organized into Time Inc. and America Online, Inc. groups. Time Inc. has two groups in chronological order. The Time Inc. library kept a run of annual reports in binders from 1923 to 1988 and another run of loose annual reports. These have not been combined.
Scope and Contents Note
Time Inc. Annual Reports includes annual reports for Time Inc. and later Time Warner Inc. after the merger in 1989. America Online, Inc. (AOL) includes reports sent to the library for use as reference at the time of that merger. Annual reports may include accompanying financial reports, fact books, or Year in Review books. Gaps in Time Inc. annual reports Annual Reports missing from Time Inc. are 2008 to 2009, 2011 to 2012, and 2014.
Accruals
If annual reports from the missing dates are located, they will be added.
Annual reports.; Corporation records.; Organization files.; Corporations -- History.; Corporations -- New York (State) -- New York.; Publishers and publishing -- New York (State) -- New York.; Time, inc. -- Archives.; Time, inc. -- History.
- Time Inc. Annual Reports, 1922-1970 (Offsite-box 656)
- Time Inc. Annual Reports, 1971-1988 (Offsite-box 657, Folder 1-10)
- Time Inc. Annual Reports, 1924-1946 (Offsite-box 657, Folder 11-12)
- Time Inc. Annual Reports, 1947-1967 (Offsite-box 658)
- Time Inc. Annual Reports, 1968-1981 (Offsite-box 659)
- Time Inc. Annual Reports, 1982-1991 (Offsite-box 660)
- Time Inc. Annual Reports, 1991-1998 (Offsite-box 661)
- Time Inc. Annual Reports, 1998-2004 (Offsite-box 662)
- Time Inc. Annual Reports, 2004-2007 (Offsite-box 663, Folder 1-7)
- Time Inc. Annual Reports, 2010 (Offsite-box 663, Folder 8)
- Time Inc. Annual Reports, 2013 (Offsite-box 663, Folder 9)
- Time Inc. Annual Reports, 2015 (Offsite-box 663, Folder 10)
- Time Inc. Annual Reports, 2016 (Offsite-box 663, Folder 11)
- America Online, Inc. Annual Reports, 1992-2000 (Offsite-box 663, Folder 12-13)